{
    "pest": {
        "HCI-Chapter_1": ["Human-Computer Interaction", "Human, Computer and Interaction", "Memex system", "Douglas Engelbert", "1962",
                         "Sketchpad", "Alto computer", "Macintosh computer", "World Wide Web", "iPhone", "Usability", "User Experience", "Accessibility", "Efficiency and Performance",
                         "Adaptability and Flexibility", "Safety and Reliability", "Ethical and Social Consideration", "Psychology", "Computer Science", "Design", "Human Factors and Ergonomics", "Cognitive Science", "Information Science", "Anthropology and Sociology", "Linguistics", "Ethnography",
                         "User-Friendly Design", "Avoiding Errors and Frustration", "Real-World Application", "Integration with the Design Process", "Legal and Safety Requirements"
                        ],
        "HCI-Chapter_2": ["Interaction", "Instructing", "Conversing", "Manipulating", "Exploring", "Responding", "Normans Seven Stages of Action", "Model", "Hassenzahl UX Model",
                        "Framework", "User Model", "Task Model", "Cognitive Model", "Interaction Model", "Word", "Visual Representation", "Physical objects or space",
                        "Time", "Behavior", "Significant", "Enjoyable", "Covenient", "Usable", "Fuctional", "Product Features", "Expercience", "Excitement", "Entry", "Engagement", "Exit", "Extension",
                        "Ergonomics", "Visibility", "Consistency", "Feedback", "Flexibility", "Constraints", "Mapping", "Affordance"
                        ],
        "DSA-Chapter_3": ["Stack", "push()", "pop()", "Infix notation", "Queues", "enqueue()", "dequeue()", "Postfix"],
        "Pur_Com-Chapter_2": ["It helps us keep in touch with family and friends anywhere in the world", "It fosters better cooperation among different cultural groups", "Gender", "Don't bad-mouth your competition",
                         "Conversations", "Handle your hashtags carefully", "Relationships", "Language", "Sharing", "Groups", "It creates opportunities for meeting new people", "Presence", "unlimited information", 
                         "Reputation", "It brings new diversity to our culture and our lives", "Identity", "Age", "Globalization", "Religious Identities", "It can make us create second lives", "Social Class", "global village",
                         "National Identities", "Ethnicity", "Be authentic and genuine", "Don't be overly promotional", "It isolates us", "Avoid over-automation", "Sharing", "Groups", "Relationship", "Presence", "Reputation", "Conversations"],
        "DSA-Chapter_4": ["Inorder", "Parent", "Right-skewed", "Height of node x", "Child Node", "Ordered", "Traversal", "Strictly Binary", "Number of edges", "Descendant", "root node", 
                         "Tree", "Depth of node x", "Full Binary Tree", "Leaf Node", "Internal nodes", "Siblings", "Root", "Weight of the node x", "Preorder", "Degree", "Degree of Tree", 
                         "Free", "0", "External", "Forest", "Left-skewed", "Postorder", "Ancestor", "Edge"],
        "HCI-Chapter-3&4": ["User Interface Design", "User Experience Design", "Scope", "User Experience", "Strategy", "Skeleton", "Structure", "Surface", "Activity Interaction", "System spanning", "Localized Interaction",
                         "Business Success", "UX Lifecycle Model", "User Experience", "Process", "Prototype Candidates", "Data modeling", "Evalute UX", "UI designer", "Cost Reduction", "UX Design Lifecycle", "Requirements Extraction", 
                         "User Experience Design", "UX Lifecycle Activities", "Generative Design", "UX Lifecycle Methods", "User Interface", "UX Lifecycle Techniques", "Overall User Satisfaction", "User-centric Approach", 
                         "User Interface Design", "Understand Needs", "Usefulness", "Design Solution", "Meaningfulness", "Emotional Impact", "UX Design Lifecycle Process", "Data Analysis", "Conceptual Design", "Data Elicitation", 
                         "Usability", "Safety and Convenience", "Design Production", "Develop Click-Through Wireframe Prototypes", "Data Organization", "Create Paper Prototype", "Propose Redisign Solution", "Analyze Evaluation Data", 
                         "Abstraction", "Collect Evaluation Data", "Intermediate Design", "Report Results", "Build Wireframes and Wireflows", "Note Taking", "Observation", "Build Physical Prototypes", "Brainstorming", "Reasoning and Deduction", "Critical Thinking and Iteration", "Framing and Reframing", "Sketching and Drawing", 
                         "Storytelling", "Prototyping and Envisioning", "Immersion", "Modeling"]
    },

    "app": {

        "HCI-Chapter_1": [
            {
                "question": "It is the study of the interface between people(user) and computers.",
                "answer": "Human-Computer Interaction",
                "id": 1
            },

            {
                "question": "To design technology systems and interface that meet user's needs and provide positive and satisfying experience.",
                "answer": "Human-Computer Interaction",
                "id": 2
            },

            {
                "question": "What are the fundamental components of HCI?",
                "answer": "Human, Computer and Interaction",
                "id": 3
            },

            {
                "question": "in 1945 Vannever Bush describes a __________, which is a precursor to hypertext.",
                "answer": "Memex system",
                "id": 4
            },

            {
                "question": "Who invented the mouse?",
                "answer": "Douglas Engelbert",
                "id": 5
            },

            {
                "question": "When Douglas Engelbert intoduce the mouse?",
                "answer": "1962",
                "id": 6
            },

            {
                "question": "In 1968 Ivan Sutherland develops __________, one of the first graphical interface",
                "answer": "Sketchpad",
                "id": 7
            },

            {
                "question": "Xerox PARC develops the __________, which features a graphical user interface similar to the Macintosh.",
                "answer": "Alto computer",
                "id": 8
            },

            {
                "question": "In 1984 the __________ is realeased, popularizing the use of graphical user interface",
                "answer": "Macintosh computer",
                "id": 10
            },

            {
                "question": "In 1993 the __________ is created, which makes it possible for people to interact with computers over the internet.",
                "answer": "World Wide Web",
                "id": 11
            },

            {
                "question": "In 2007 the __________ was released, which populized the use of touchscreens for HCI.",
                "answer": "iPhone",
                "id": 12
            },

            {
                "question": "The first augmented reality (Ar) headset was __________, which opened up new possibilities for HCI.",
                "answer": "Google Glass",
                "id": 13
            },

            {
                "question": "The goal is to create interfaces and interactions that are intuitive, efficient, and enjoyable for users, ultimately leading to a positive user experience and increased user satisfaction.",
                "answer": "Usability",
                "id": 14
            },

            {
                "question": "Refers to the overall experience and perception that a user has when interacting with a computer system, software application, website, or any digital product.",
                "answer": "User Experience",
                "id": 15
            },

            {
                "question": "Refers to the design and implementation of digital products, software applications, websites, and other technology interfaces in a way that ensures equal access and usability for individuals with disabilities.",
                "answer": "Accessibility",
                "id": 16
            },

            {
                "question": "These are essential aspects of Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) that focus on how well a system or interface performs and how efficiently users can accomplish their tasks",
                "answer": "Efficiency and Performance",
                "id": 17
            },

            {
                "question": "__________ are critical aspects of Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) that focus on ensuring that technology interfaces and systems are dependable, secure, and free from errors that could lead to harm or undesirable consequences for users.",
                "answer": "Safety and Reliability",
                "id": 18
            },

            {
                "question": "__________ are important concepts in Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) that focus on designing interfaces and systems that can accommodate a wide range of user needs, preferences, and changing conditions",
                "answer": "Adaptability and Flexibility",
                "id": 19
            },

            {
                "question": "HCI professionals and designers must be mindful of the ethical implications and broader societal impacts of their work.",
                "answer": "Ethical and Social Consideration",
                "id": 20
            },

            {
                "question": "__________ helps HCI professionals better understand and design technology interfaces that are more effective, user-friendly, and tailored to human cognitive and emotional processes.",
                "answer": "Psychology",
                "id": 21
            },

            {
                "question": "This  collaborate closely with HCI designers, psychologists, and other professionals to create technology interfaces that are not only technically sound but also user-centered and aligned with human needs and behavior.",
                "answer": "Computer Science",
                "id": 22
            },

            {
                "question": "It involves the planning, creation, and optimization of technology interfaces to ensure that they are user-friendly, visually appealing, and effective in facilitating user interactions.",
                "answer": "Design",
                "id": 23
            },

            {
                "question": "It focuses on optimizing the design of technology interfaces, systems, and physical environments to enhance human performance, safety, and well-being.",
                "answer": "Human Factors and Ergonomics",
                "id": 24
            },

            {
                "question": "Understanding how humans think, perceive, learn, and make decisions is essential for designing user-friendly and effective technology interfaces.",
                "answer": "Cognitive Science",
                "id": 25
            },

            {
                "question": "It focusing on the organization, retrieval, and use of information within technology interfaces. HCI professionals often draw from Information Science principles to create interfaces that facilitate efficient information access and management.",
                "answer": "Information Science",
                "id": 26
            },

            {
                "question": "Understanding human behavior, social interactions, and cultural norms is essential for designing technology interfaces and systems that align with the needs and values of diverse user populations.",
                "answer": "Anthropology and Sociology",
                "id": 27
            },

            {
                "question": "It focusing on the study of language and communication, which are essential components of human-computer interactions. Understanding linguistic principles is crucial for designing technology interfaces that facilitate effective communication between users and machines.",
                "answer": "Linguistics",
                "id": 28
            },

            {
                "question": "Helps HCI professionals gain a deep understanding of users' behaviors, needs, and cultural contexts.",
                "answer": "Ethnography",
                "id": 29
            },

            {
                "question": "HCI professionals create technology interfaces and systems that are not only functional but also enjoyable, efficient, and accessible to a wide range of users, ultimately leading to a positive and user-friendly experience.",
                "answer": "User-Friendly Design",
                "id": 30
            },

            {
                "question": " User-friendly interfaces should be designed to minimize the occurrence of errors and help users recover from them smoothly",
                "answer": "Avoiding Errors and Frustration",
                "id": 31
            },

            {
                "question": "HCI professionals and researchers continue to innovate and adapt principles to address emerging technologies and changing user needs in these and other domains, making technology more accessible, usable, and enjoyable for users.",
                "answer": "Real-World Application",
                "id": 32
            },

            {
                "question": "By integrating HCI throughout the design process, designers and developers can create technology interfaces and systems that prioritize user needs, are intuitive and accessible, and ultimately provide a positive and effective user experience. This iterative and user-centered approach contributes to the success of the product in the real world.",
                "answer": "Integration with the Design Process",
                "id": 33
            },

            {
                "question": "Designing and developing technology interfaces and systems. Compliance with relevant laws and safety standards is essential to protect users, ensure ethical practices, and avoid legal consequences.",
                "answer": "Legal and Safety Requirements",
                "id": 34
            }
        ],

        "HCI-Chapter_2": [
            {
                "question": "Refers to the dynamic exchange of information and actions between a user and a computer or digital system.",
                "answer": "Interaction",
                "id": 35
            },

            {
                "question": "Users provide explicit commands or instructions to a computer system to perform specific actions",
                "answer": "Instructing",
                "id": 37
            },

            {
                "question": "Expecting response from the computer",
                "answer": "Conversing",
                "id": 38
            },

            {
                "question": "Cotrolling software applications",
                "answer": "Manipulating",
                "id": 39
            },

            {
                "question": "Navigating or discovering the system or application.",
                "answer": "Exploring",
                "id": 40
            },

            {
                "question": "Responding of a computer to the user and vice versa.",
                "answer": "Responding",
                "id": 41
            },

            {
                "question": "This model is widely used in the field of Human-Computer Interaction (HCI) and user experience (UX) design to understand how users interact with systems and how design can influence the user experience.",
                "answer": "Normans Seven Stages of Action",
                "id": 42
            },

            {
                "question": "__________ is a framework used to understand and evaluate the user experience (UX) in interactive products and systems. This model emphasizes that the user experience goes beyond usability and functionality, considering the emotional and hedonic aspects of user interactions.",
                "answer": "Hassenzahl UX Model",
                "id": 43
            },

            {
                "question": "__________ help to describe and explain various facets of human-computer interaction.",
                "answer": "Model",
                "id": 44
            },

            {
                "question": "__________ in HCI provides a structured approach, set of principles, or guidelines for designing, evaluating, or analyzing aspects of human-computer interaction.",
                "answer": "Framework",
                "id": 45
            },

            {
                "question": "__________ represent the characteristics, behaviors, and needs of the users who interact with a computer system. They are used to design interfaces that match the user's mental model and expectations.",
                "answer": "User Model",
                "id": 46
            },

            {
                "question": "__________ delve into the mental processes and cognitive aspects involved in human-computer interaction. They aim to understand how users think, perceive, learn, and make decisions when using computer systems",
                "answer": "Cognitive Model",
                "id": 47
            },

            {
                "question": "__________ describe the sequence of actions and steps that users take to complete specific tasks or goals using a computer system. These models help designers create interfaces that support efficient task execution",
                "answer": "Task Model",
                "id": 48
            },

            {
                "question": "__________ illustrate the patterns and sequences of user actions and system responses during interaction. They are used to design interfaces that facilitate smooth and effective user-system communication.",
                "answer": "Interaction Model",
                "id": 49
            },

            {
                "question": "What does 1D means in Five Dimensions of Interaction Design",
                "answer": "Word",
                "id": 50
            },

            {
                "question": "What does 2D means in Five Dimensions of Interaction Design",
                "answer": "Visual Representation",
                "id": 51
            },

            {
                "question": "What does 3D means in Five Dimensions of Interaction Design",
                "answer": "Physical objects or space",
                "id": 52
            },

            {
                "question": "What does 4D means in Five Dimensions of Interaction Design",
                "answer": "Time",
                "id": 53
            },

            {
                "question": "What does 5D means in Five Dimensions of Interaction Design",
                "answer": "Behavior",
                "id": 54
            },

            {
                "question": "in this level in UX design pyramid, the application is working.",
                "answer": "Functional",
                "id": 55
            },

            {
                "question": "in this level in UX design pyramid, you are using the app to accomplish a task.",
                "answer": "Usable",
                "id": 56
            },

            {
                "question": "in this level in UX design pyramid, you are now using the app more than you need.",
                "answer": "Convenient",
                "id": 57
            },

            {
                "question": "in this level in UX design pyramid, you are now relying on this app.",
                "answer": "Enjoyable",
                "id": 58
            },

            {
                "question": "in this level in UX design pyramid, you can't live without this app.",
                "answer": "Significant",
                "id": 59
            },

            {
                "question": "The one whom computer systems are designed to assist.",
                "answer": "Human",
                "id": 60
            },

            {
                "question": "It a type of memory that stores information from the senses for a very short period of time.",
                "answer": "Sensory Memory",
                "id": 61
            },

            {
                "question": "In this phase in 5E Experience Design Model, the application is now deployed",
                "answer": "Entry",
                "id": 62
            },

            {
                "question": "In this phase in 5E Experience Design Model, the team will organizing events and other strategies to keep users using the app",
                "answer": "Engagement",
                "id": 63
            },

            {
                "question": "This the fourth phase in 5E Experience Design Model",
                "answer": "Exit",
                "id": 64
            },

            {
                "question": "In this phase in 5E Experience Design Model, the application has a extra features to keep the user using their app. ex. notifications, event, daily rewards.",
                "answer": "Extension",
                "id": 65
            },

            {
                "question": "In this phase in 5E Experience Design Model, the team is makig a promotional events like advertisement before deploying the app",
                "answer": "Excitement",
                "id": 66
            },

            {
                "question": "__________, also known as human factors engineering, aims to create systems and environments that are comfortable, efficient, safe, and conducive to human well-being during computer use.",
                "answer": "Ergonomics",
                "id": 67
            },

            {
                "question": "It is the basic principle that the more visible an element is, the more likely user will know about them and how to use them.",
                "answer": "Visibility",
                "id": 68
            },

            {
                "question": "It is the principle of making it clear to the user what action has been taken and what has been accomplished.",
                "answer": "Feedback",
                "id": 69
            },

            {
                "question": "Is a about limiting the range of iteraction possibilities for the user to simplify the interface and guide the user to appropriate next action.",
                "answer": "Constraints",
                "id": 70
            },

            {
                "question": "Refers to having similar operations and similar elements for achieving similar tasks.",
                "answer": "Consistency",
                "id": 71
            },

            {
                "question": "Is about having a clear realationship between controls and the effect they have on the world.",
                "answer": "Mapping",
                "id": 72
            },

            {
                "question": "Refers to the attribute of the objects that allows people to know how to use it",
                "answer": "Affordance",
                "id": 73
            },
            {
                "question": "The first step of how our memory stores information.",
                "answer": "Sensory memories",
                "id": 74
            },

            {
                "question": "This action is needed to store the sensory into Short-term memory or working memory.",
                "answer": "Attention",
                "id": 75
            },

            {
                "question": "When you give an attention into information, that information will now store in to.?",
                "answer": "Short-term memory",
                "id": 76
            },

            {
                "question": "We need this so we can store this information in to long-term memory",
                "answer": "Rehearsal",
                "id": 77
            },

            {
                "question": "It is a temporary storage system that holds information that is currently being used.",
                "answer": "Short-term memory",
                "id": 78
            },

            {
                "question": "It is the inability to acces information from our memory.",
                "answer": "Forgetting",
                "id": 79
            },

            {
                "question": "It is what we called when we accessing information from our memory",
                "answer": "Retrieval",
                "id": 80
            },

            {
                "question": "You are storing or putting information to your memory",
                "answer": "Storing",
                "id": 81
            },

            {
                "question": "Using knowledge to draw conclusion or infer new information",
                "answer": "Reasoning",
                "id": 82
            },

            {
                "question": "Derives a logically necessary conclusion from given premises, even if it doesn't always align with our notion of truth.",
                "answer": "Deductive",
                "id": 83
            },

            {
                "question": "Generalized from observed cases to infer information about unobserved cases, although it may not be entirely reilable.",
                "answer": "Inductive",
                "id": 84
            },

            {
                "question": "Reasons from a fact to the cause of the fact, helping us derive explanations for observed events",
                "answer": "Abductive",
                "id": 85
            },

            {
                "question": "It is process of finding a solution to an unfamiliar task using the knowledge we have.",
                "answer": "Problem-solving",
                "id": 86
            },

            {
                "question": "In this theory, you are deviding or restructuring the problem and gaining insight to find innovattive solutions.",
                "answer": "Gestalt theory",
                "id": 87
            },

            {
                "question": "We called it a trial and error theory.",
                "answer": "Problem space theory",
                "id": 88
            },

            {
                "question": "Refers to the process of gaining experties and proficiency in a particular domain over time. It is a complex process that involves a number of factors.",
                "answer": "Skill acquisition",
                "id": 89
            },

            {
                "question": "It is a factor in skill acquisition that said, you are gaining skill through teaching",
                "answer": "Transfer",
                "id": 90
            },

            {
                "question": "__________ are unintentional actions that devirate from the desired outcome. They can range from minor inconveniences to serious consequences.",
                "answer": "Errors",
                "id": 91
            },

            {
                "question": "This component represents how humans gather information from the environment. It involves sensory processes such as vision, hearing, touch, and other senses.",
                "answer": "Perceptual system",
                "id": 92
            },

            {
                "question": "It is responsible for executing physical actions in response to the information processed by the cognitive system.",
                "answer": "motor system",
                "id": 93
            },

            {
                "question": "It is responsible for tasks such as memory, attention, problem-solving, decision-making, and language processing. It processes the information received from the perceptual system and generates actions based on that information.",
                "answer": "cognitive system",
                "id": 94
            },

            {
                "question": "refers to the sensory memory associated with visual information. It is extremely short-lived, lasting only for a fraction of a second (typically less than a second).",
                "answer": "iconic memory",
                "id": 95
            },

            {
                "question": "the sensory memory associated with auditory information, such as sounds and spoken language. It lasts longer than iconic memory, typically around 2 to 4 seconds",
                "answer": "Echoic Memory",
                "id": 96
            },

            {
                "question": "This sensory information helps you recognize objects, navigate your environment, and perform various tactile tasks.",
                "answer": "Haptic Memory",
                "id": 97
            },

            {
                "question": "Refers to the system responsible for encoding, storing, and retrieving personal experiences and specific events or episodes in your life",
                "answer": "Episodic Memory",
                "id": 98
            },
            
            {
                "question": " It involves the storage of factual knowledge, concepts, and information that are not tied to specific personal experiences. This type of memory encompasses a wide range of information, such as facts, concepts, language, and general knowledge about the world.",
                "answer": "Semantic Memory",
                "id": 99
            }
        ],

        "DSA-Chapter_3": [
            {
                "question": "Add (store) an item to the queue.",
                "answer": "enqueue()",
                "id": 100
            },

            {
                "question": "Last-in-First-out",
                "answer": "Stack",
                "id": 101
            },

            {
                "question": "It is the insertion operation in Stack",
                "answer": "push()",
                "id": 102
            },

            {
                "question": "Removal operation in Stack",
                "answer": "pop()",
                "id": 103
            },

            {
                "question": "Get the top data element of the stack, without removing it. In Stack",
                "answer": "peek()",
                "id": 104
            },

            {
                "question": "Check if stack is full",
                "answer": "isFull()",
                "id": 105
            },

            {
                "question": "Check if stack is empty.",
                "answer": "isEmpty()",
                "id": 106
            },

            {
                "question": "First-In-First-Out (FIFO)",
                "answer": "Queues",
                "id": 107
            },

            {
                "question": "Remove (access) an item from the queue.",
                "answer": "dequeue()",
                "id": 108
            },

            {
                "question": "Gets the element at the front of the queue without removing it;",
                "answer": "peek()",
                "id": 109
            },

            {
                "question": "Infix notation is the traditional notation, and it has several advantages, but it also requires extensive rules regarding the order of operation.",
                "answer": "Infix notation",
                "id": 110
            },

            {
                "question": "Places the operator after the two operands. The operators appear in the order in which they are to be executed",
                "answer": "Postfix",
                "id": 111
            },

            {
                "question": "The __________ provides top value of the stack without actually removing it.",
                "answer": "top pointer",
                "id": 112
            },

            {
                "question": " uses a linked list to implement a stack of",
                "answer": "strings.LinkStackOfJava.java",
                "id": 113
            },

            {
                "question": "Like Stack, we maintain a reference first to the __________ added Node in the queue.",
                "answer": "least recently",
                "id": 114
            },

            {
                "question": "A stack implementations that allows us to build a stack of one particular type, such String.",
                "answer": "Generics",
                "id": 115
            },

            {
                "question": "Java supplies built-in object types known as __________, one for each of primitive types: Boolean, Integer, Double, Character.",
                "answer": "wrapper types",
                "id": 116
            },

            {
                "question": "int to Integer",
                "answer": "Autoboxing",
                "id": 118
            },

            {
                "question": "Integer to int",
                "answer": "unboxing",
                "id": 119
            },

            {
                "question": "Access all of the item in the collection, one at a time, without deleting them.",
                "answer": "Iteration",
                "id": 120
            },

            {
                "question": "It is the traditional notation, and it has several advantages, but it also requires extensive rules regarding the order of operation.",
                "answer": "infix notation",
                "id": 121
            },

            {
                "question": "It is in __________ if every subexpression to be evaluated is of the form operand-operator.",
                "answer": "postfix form",
                "id": 122
            },

            {
                "question": "An expression is in __________ if every subexpression to be evaluated is of the form operand-operator-operand",
                "answer": "infix form",
                "id": 123
            }
        ],

        "Pur_Com-Chapter_2": [
            {
                "question": "The process of bringing people together and making them interact and exchange ideas across traditional borders.",
                "answer": "Globalization",
                "id": 125
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The world driven largely by advances in technology, has become inextricably interconnected across distances and other boundaries",
                "answer": "Globalization",
                "id": 126
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Is the spread of products, technology, information, and jobs across national borders and cultures.",
                "answer": "Globalization",
                "id": 127
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Is the process of interaction and integration among people, companies, and governments worldwide.",
                "answer": "Globalization",
                "id": 128
            },
            
            {
                "question": " ________ is a process of interaction and integration among the people, companies, and governments of different nations. A process driven by international trade and investment and aided by information technology.",
                "answer": "Globalization",
                "id": 129
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Due to globalization, the so-called ________ (Marshall McLuhan’s prediction) has emerged and has come to reality--- this is a world interconnected by an electronic nervous system.",
                "answer": "global village",
                "id": 130
            },
            
            {
                "question": "What used to take someone hours of searching through a library can now be done within a matter of seconds on the Internet. Whatever questions you have you can generally get an instant answer on the computer. One word of caution though: Make sure that the website you visit and/or the source of the information is credible!",
                "answer": "unlimited information",
                "id": 131
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Many applications online are currently available for meeting new people anytime anywhere in the world. The applications vary--from posting photos and videos like Instagram, to social networking like Twitter, games like Game of War, or entertainment like textPlus Communities. You should, however, be careful about things that you post on the Internet or about getting too close with an online acquaintance whom you have neither met nor known much more before or else you may eventually find yourself in some kind of predicament.",
                "answer": "It creates opportunities for meeting new people",
                "id": 132
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Our being in the 21 century is great; many incredible communication tools have been developed. The tools allow us to get in touch with family and friends, even strangers, anytime anywhere. Computers, smart phones, iPads, and email, besides the dependable SMS (text message), allow us to communicate quickly and easily.",
                "answer": "It helps us keep in touch with family and friends anywhere in the world",
                "id": 133
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The pace of change caused by technology is blinding. Google recipes, and anyone, like you and your classmate, can put sumptuous meals on the dining table. Your cell phone, with its digital camera, has replaced the film camera, and you yourself can print your own pictures without any help from the almost-extinct film developer.",
                "answer": "It brings new diversity to our culture and our lives",
                "id": 134
            },
            
            {
                "question": "New technologies help companies extend participation on a project to an ever-greater number of people, allowing firms to tap into a wide body of knowledge and expertise.",
                "answer": "It fosters better cooperation among different cultural groups",
                "id": 135
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Mobile communication is so powerful that it changes not only what we do so, but also what we are. Wherever we are, our mobile phones are also there-we are inseparable. At the dinner table with our families, in a meeting at work, during interactions in the classroom, while shopping in malls, in conversations with friends, while listening to presentations in lectures-everywhere, even at the most unlikely places like funerals--the cell phone takes us away from the people around us. It literally isolates us from the rest of the world... from humanity.",
                "answer": "It isolates us",
                "id": 136
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Millions of people find solace in virtual communities where they have found a second life. You might have heard of Sim City, Farmville, and Cities Skylines. In these social networking sites, users or players create or choose avatars to interact with other users anywhere in the world.",
                "answer": "It can make us create second lives",
                "id": 137
            },
            
            {
                "question": "________ is probably the most important element in the communication chain.",
                "answer": "Language",
                "id": 138
            },
            
            {
                "question": "In a multiethnic world, ethnicity is as important as language. Often misunderstandings crop up from ethnic differences.",
                "answer": "Ethnicity",
                "id": 139
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The concept of nationhood is a very complicated proposition. The concept of national pride at times inundates other humane considerations",
                "answer": "National Identities",
                "id": 140
            },
            
            {
                "question": "History has been witnessed to the fact that religion has played the role of the biggest human divisive force. If we take a sneak peek into the history of humanity, we would be able to find out that religion has been the single largest cause of conflicts. Whether we talk about the crusades or deliberate about the current religious unrests, religion has fomented the maximum trouble among fellow human beings. To tackle it, the best way is to have a personal take on religion. Human beings need to appreciate that differences in religious orientations are natural and the same should not deter people from having communication and forging collaborations.",
                "answer": "Religious Identities",
                "id": 141
            },
            
            {
                "question": "No wonder that social positioning and economic status of people put them into certain brackets. This artificial division again creates rifts between the haves and have-nots thereby leading to a breakage in the communication chain. All throughout the world, the existence of different social classes is a crude reality. Let us take an Indian example. As the pandemic keeps getting worse, the biggest victims have been the migrant laborers. The reason why this class has taken the toll is their economic and social status. The best way to deal with this differentiation is to reduce the gap between the social classes.",
                "answer": "Social Class",
                "id": 142
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Let us now come to gender. As basic as it is, the reality remains that gender can also become an impediment for the flow of communication at times. The difference between genders across the world is very real. In India, the transgender community must face social ostracism all the time. The communication channel in this case is broken. There is hardly any discourse on the community. The best way to deal with this stalemate is to accept that gender cant be the basis of any discrimination. However, like many other things, it is easier said than done.",
                "answer": "Gender",
                "id": 143
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Across societies, generational shifts can cause a lot of miscommunications. As the world changes, meanings and communication channels change. At times, older people cant cope with these changes, which in turn creates an imbalance in communication. At other times, the younger generation fails to understand the frame of reference of the older people thereby creating an unnecessary rift.",
                "answer": "Age",
                "id": 144
            },
            
            {
                "question": "This is the most basic functional block of social media. It represents the extent to which users reveal their identities in a social media setting and can include information like name, age, gender, profession, location, and also information that portrays users in certain ways",
                "answer": "Identity",
                "id": 145
            },
            
            {
                "question": "How do users communicate with other users in a social media setting? Many facilitate conversations among individuals and groups (i.e. Twitter's #hashtags, *cue Jimmy Fallon*). These conversations happen for variety of reasons such as to meet like-minded people, to find love, to build their self-esteem, or to be news-breakers on innovative ideas or trending topics.",
                "answer": "Conversations",
                "id": 146
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Social often implies an exchange between people, which in turn means sharing. We now distribute and receive more content in less time than all of humanity has done previously. What are the implications on the social media sites that mediate these ties?",
                "answer": "Sharing",
                "id": 147
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Have you ever checked Facebook or Foursquare to find out where your friends are? The presence block refers to the accessibility of which you can know where others are, virtually and/or physically, through status updates or check-ins. This social media building block has benefited from the world's hyper-connectivity and bridged the gap between virtual and physical.",
                "answer": "Presence",
                "id": 148
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The relationships block is straightforward. It represents a connection between more than one user through conversation, sharing information, meeting up, or just listing each other as a follower or friend. Consequently, this can lead to duping, such as catfishing. Everything has its evils.",
                "answer": "Relationships",
                "id": 149
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Reputation can have different meanings on social media platforms, but at its core it's a sense of identifying the status of others and yourself in a social network. The study states that reputation is a matter of trust. Do you think so?",
                "answer": "Reputation",
                "id": 150
            },
            
            {
                "question": "What communities and sub-communities exist on a social media platform, and how easy are they to construct? As your network becomes bigger with friends, followers, and contacts, it becomes necessary to sort your cronies into different groups. This is exemplified in Twitter's lists and Facebook's public, private, and secret groups.",
                "answer": "Groups",
                "id": 151
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Try not to message all your customers asking them to buy your products and avoid sharing constant advertisements on your page. Make your social profiles a blend of promotional and valuable content.",
                "answer": "Dont be overly promotional",
                "id": 152
            },
            
            {
                "question": "While scheduling your posts in advance and automating analytics is helpful, dont automate everything. Some things still need a human touch.",
                "answer": "Avoid over-automation",
                "id": 153
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Avoid using too many hashtags at once. Even on Instagram, where you can use 30 hashtags in a single caption, its important not to overdo it",
                "answer": "Handle your hashtags carefully",
                "id": 154
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Dont be petty. Saying negative things about your competitors online will harm your reputation more than it hurts theirs.",
                "answer": "Dont bad-mouth your competition",
                "id": 155
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Dont try to be something youre not. Remember that your customers can learn whatever they need to know about your brand online today and things like authenticity can go a long way",
                "answer": "Be authentic and genuine",
                "id": 156
            },

            {
                "question": "The extent to which users know if others are available",
                "answer": "Presence",
                "id": 157
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The extent to which users relate to each other",
                "answer": "Relationship",
                "id": 158
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The extent to which users know the social standing of others and content",
                "answer": "Reputation",
                "id": 159
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The extent to which users are ordered or form communications",
                "answer": "Groups",
                "id": 160
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The extent to which users communicate with each other",
                "answer": "Conversations",
                "id": 161
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The extent to which users exchange, distribute and receive content",
                "answer": "Sharing",
                "id": 162
            }
        ],

        "DSA-Chapter_4": [
            {
                "question": "a nonlinear data structure.",
                "answer": "Tree",
                "id": 163
            },
            
            {
                "question": "A structure consisting of one node called the root and zero or one or more subtrees.",
                "answer": "Tree",
                "id": 164
            },
            
            {
                "question": "One node of the tree is designated as ________.",
                "answer": "root node",
                "id": 165
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The _______ node is the topmost node in the tree hierarchy. The one that doesnt have a parent.",
                "answer": "Root",
                "id": 166
            },
            
            {
                "question": "If the node is descendant of any node, then the node is know as a ________.",
                "answer": "Child Node",
                "id": 167
            },
            
            {
                "question": "If the node contains any sub-node, then that node is said to be the ________ of that sub-node.",
                "answer": "Parent",
                "id": 168
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The nodes that the same parents are know as ________.",
                "answer": "Siblings",
                "id": 169
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The node of the tree that doesnt have any child node. It is the bottom most node of the tree. And also called external nodes.",
                "answer": "Leaf Node",
                "id": 170
            },
            
            {
                "question": "A node that has at least one child node.",
                "answer": "Internal nodes",
                "id": 171
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Any predecessor node on a path from the root to that node.",
                "answer": "Ancestor",
                "id": 172
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The immediate successor of the given node is know as a ________ of a node.",
                "answer": "Descendant",
                "id": 173
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The total number of children of a node.",
                "answer": "Degree",
                "id": 174
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The highest degree of the node among all the nodes in a tree is call ________.",
                "answer": "Degree of Tree",
                "id": 175
            },
            
            {
                "question": "If there are n nodes, then there would n-1 edges.",
                "answer": "Number of edges",
                "id": 176
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Node incoming link",
                "answer": "Edge",
                "id": 177
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Can be defined as the leangth of the path from the root to the node x. The number of edges between the root node and the nood x.",
                "answer": "Depth of node x",
                "id": 178
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The root node has ________ depth.",
                "answer": "0",
                "id": 179
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Can be defined as the longest path from the node x to the leaf node.",
                "answer": "Height of node x",
                "id": 180
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Described by the value of the node multiplied by the level",
                "answer": "Weight of the node x",
                "id": 181
            },
            
            {
                "question": "An ________ tree is a finite set.",
                "answer": "Ordered",
                "id": 182
            },
            
            {
                "question": "A ________ tree has no node designated as the root and the orientation from a node to any other node is insignificant.",
                "answer": "Free",
                "id": 183
            },
            
            {
                "question": "When zero or more disjoint trees are taken together, they are know as a _______.",
                "answer": "Forest",
                "id": 184
            },
            
            {
                "question": "A node is ________ if it has no children, otherwise it is internal.",
                "answer": "External",
                "id": 185
            },
            
            {
                "question": "If two nodes have same parents, they are said to be ________.",
                "answer": "Siblings",
                "id": 186
            },
            
            {
                "question": "A type of binary tree tha has no right subtree.",
                "answer": "Left-skewed",
                "id": 187
            },
            
            {
                "question": "A type of binary tree that has no left subtree.",
                "answer": "Right-skewed",
                "id": 188
            },
            
            {
                "question": "A type of binary tree that is a tree in which every node has either two subtrees or none at all.",
                "answer": "Strictly Binary",
                "id": 189
            },
            
            {
                "question": "A strictly binary tree in which all terminal nodes lie at the bottommost level.",
                "answer": "Full Binary Tree",
                "id": 190
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Is a procedure that visits the nodes of the binary tree in a linear fashion such that each node is visited exactly once, where visit is defined as performing computations local to the node.",
                "answer": "Traversal",
                "id": 191
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The root is visited first. Root-Left-Right",
                "answer": "Preorder",
                "id": 192
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Left-Root-Right",
                "answer": "Inorder",
                "id": 193
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Left-Right-Root",
                "answer": "Postorder",
                "id": 194
            }
        ],

        "HCI-Chapter-3&4": [
            {
                "question": "Who and why are you designing for? (Users needs and Product Objectives)",
                "answer": "Strategy",
                "id": 195
            },
            
            {
                "question": "What are you designing, what the solutions does? (Features and COntent Requirements)",
                "answer": "Scope",
                "id": 196
            },
            
            {
                "question": "How the product or solution works, create a blueprint on how the user interact with it? (Interaction Design and information Architecture)",
                "answer": "Structure",
                "id": 197
            },
            
            {
                "question": "First interface of the solution, or the tangible elements of the ux? (Information, interface and Navigation Design)",
                "answer": "Skeleton",
                "id": 198
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The most visible element. The users see and interact with? (Visual design)",
                "answer": "Surface",
                "id": 199
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The overall feelings of the user using the design or system.",
                "answer": "User Experience",
                "id": 200
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The process of creating products and experience that help users get done what theyve come to do. Satisfying users needs.",
                "answer": "User Experience Design",
                "id": 201
            },
            
            {
                "question": "It focuses on looks of the system",
                "answer": "User Interface Design",
                "id": 202
            },

            {
                "question": "This interaction is one purpose only or limited action",
                "answer": "Localized Interaction",
                "id": 203
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Perform many task in in one activity",
                "answer": "Activity-based Interaction",
                "id": 204
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Type of interaction that has more interactions. Like gcash in shopee",
                "answer": "System spanning",
                "id": 205
            },

            {
                "question": "The totality of effects felt by the user as a result of interaction.",
                "answer": "User Experience",
                "id": 206
            },
            
            {
                "question": "It is the visual and interactive elements of a product or service.",
                "answer": "User Interface",
                "id": 207
            },
            
            {
                "question": "It refers ti the visual elements that allow user to interact with a product.",
                "answer": "User Interface",
                "id": 208
            },
            
            {
                "question": "It the process of creating products and services that are easy to use, enjoyable to use, and meet the needs of the users.",
                "answer": "User Experience Design",
                "id": 209
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Is the process of designing the visual and interactive elements of a product or service.",
                "answer": "User Interface Design",
                "id": 210
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Reponsible for Visual design",
                "answer": "UI designer",
                "id": 211
            },
            
            {
                "question": "________ refers to the positive impact that a well-designed user experience can have on a company's profitability, growth, and competitiveness.",
                "answer": "Business Success",
                "id": 212
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The use of prototype to reduce resources.",
                "answer": "Cost Reduction",
                "id": 213
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Designing interfaces and interactions that prioritize user safety, security, and ease of use.",
                "answer": "Safety and Convenience",
                "id": 214
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Refers to how well a product or system meets users' needs, expectations, and preferences, resulting in a positive user experience.",
                "answer": "Overall User Satisfaction",
                "id": 215
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Involves placing the needs and preferences of users at the forefront of the design and development process.",
                "answer": "User-centric Approach",
                "id": 216
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Productivity, efficiency, ease of use, learnability.",
                "answer": "Usability",
                "id": 217
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Ability to use system or product to accomplish goals of work.",
                "answer": "Usefulness",
                "id": 218
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Affective component of user experience and user feelings, user satisfaction.",
                "answer": "Emotional Impact",
                "id": 219
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Long-term personal relationship with product.",
                "answer": "Meaningfulness",
                "id": 220
            },
            
            {
                "question": "A step-by-step approach followed to create user-centered experience and prototypes, from unnderstanding user needs to evaluating the final design.",
                "answer": "Process",
                "id": 221
            },
            
            {
                "question": "It is cycle that emcompasses the process of designing a user experience, starting from ideation to deployment and beyond.",
                "answer": "UX Design Lifecycle",
                "id": 222
            },
            
            {
                "question": "It is a depiction of how the activities of the lifecycle are organized and arrange in chronological.",
                "answer": "UX Design Lifecycle Process",
                "id": 223
            },
            
            {
                "question": "It is a structured framework that guides the process of designing a user experience.",
                "answer": "UX Lifecycle Model",
                "id": 224
            },
            
            {
                "question": "These are the essential tasks and steps that are performed during the process of creating a user experience.",
                "answer": "UX Lifecycle Activities",
                "id": 225
            },
            
            {
                "question": "These are the different approaches used to carry out the main activities or subactivities in the user experience design process.",
                "answer": "UX Lifecycle Methods",
                "id": 226
            },
            
            {
                "question": "These are specific, detailed practices used to perform individual steps within the activities, subactivities, or methods of the user experience design process.",
                "answer": "UX Lifecycle Techniques",
                "id": 227
            },
            
            {
                "question": "This activity involves gaining insights into users, their work practices, usage patterns, and the subject-matter domain to understand their needs and requirements for the design.",
                "answer": "Understand Needs",
                "id": 228
            },
            
            {
                "question": "In this activity, designer create designs as solutions to address the identified user needs and challenges.",
                "answer": "Design Solution",
                "id": 229
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Designers build prototypes of promising design solutions to visualize and test their effectiveness.",
                "answer": "Prototype Candidates",
                "id": 230
            },
            
            {
                "question": "This activity involves verifying and refining the designs based on user feedback and insight to ensure a positive user experience.",
                "answer": "Evalute UX",
                "id": 231
            },
            
            {
                "question": "This involves interviewing and observing users while they work to gather data about their practices, preference, and needs.",
                "answer": "Data Elicitation",
                "id": 232
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The collected usage research data is distilled and organized for better comprehension.",
                "answer": "Data Analysis",
                "id": 233
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Representation are created to capture user characteristics, information, flow, tasks, and work environments. These model aid collaboration, sharing, archival, rehearsal, and immension.",
                "answer": "Data modeling",
                "id": 234
            },
            
            {
                "question": "This subacitivity invloves codifying the needs and requirements identified during the reseach process.",
                "answer": "Requirements Extraction",
                "id": 235
            },
            
            {
                "question": "In This sub-activity, designers engage in ideation and sketching to create various design ideas.",
                "answer": "Generative Design",
                "id": 236
            },
            
            {
                "question": "This sub-activity involves creating mental models, system models, and storyboards to flesh out the design concepts.",
                "answer": "Conceptual Design",
                "id": 237
            },
            
            {
                "question": "This sub-activity focuses on specifying detailed plans for implementing the selected design.",
                "answer": "Design Production",
                "id": 238
            },

            {
                "question": "In this place, desingers develop ecological, interaction, and emotional design plans for the most promising candidates.",
                "answer": "Intermediate Design",
                "id": 239
            },
            
            {
                "question": "DEsigners develop hand-drawn or printed paper prototypes to explore and visualize design concepts in low fidelity.",
                "answer": "Create Paper Prototype",
                "id": 240
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Designers create basic visual representations of the user interface and interaction flow.",
                "answer": "Build Wireframes and Wireflows",
                "id": 241
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Desingers create interactive prototypes that allow users to navigate through the design with clickable elements, providing a more dynamic representation of the user experience.",
                "answer": "Develop Click-Through Wireframe Prototypes",
                "id": 242
            },
            
            {
                "question": "For physical products or tangible interactions, designers create physical prototyes to test and evaluate the designs functionality and usability.",
                "answer": "Build Physical Prototypes",
                "id": 243
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Desingers use various methods, such as user testing, surveys, or analysis, to gather data on how users interact with the design. This data provides valuable insights into user behavior and preferences.",
                "answer": "Collect Evaluation Data",
                "id": 244
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The collected daya is analyzed to identify patterns, official incidents, and root causes. This analysis helps designers understand the strengths and weakness of the design.",
                "answer": "Analyze Evaluation Data",
                "id": 245
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Based on the evaluation results, designers propose changes and improvements to address identified issues and enhance the user experience.",
                "answer": "Propose Redisign Solution",
                "id": 246
            },
            
            {
                "question": "The evaluation findings and proposed redesign solution solution are documented and communicated to stakeholders and the design team. This ensures everyone knows the evaluation outcomes and the design team. This ensures everyone knows the evaluation outcomes and the next steps for refining the design.",
                "answer": "Report Results",
                "id": 247
            },
            
            {
                "question": "Involves keenly and objectively watching people, events, or situations to gather information and insights.",
                "answer": "Observation",
                "id": 248
            },
            
            {
                "question": "is the process of simplifying complex information or concepts into more manageable and understandable forms.",
                "answer": "Abstraction",
                "id": 249
            },
            
            {
                "question": "involves recording important information, ideas, or observations for future reference or organization.",
                "answer": "Note Taking",
                "id": 250
            },
            
            {
                "question": " is the skill of structuring and categorizing information logically and efficiently.",
                "answer": "Data Organization",
                "id": 251
            },

            {
                "question": "entails creating representations or visualizations of objects, systems, or processes to understand them better.",
                "answer": "Modeling",
                "id": 252
            },
            
            {
                "question": "is the art of conveying information, ideas, or experiences through narratives that engage and captivate an audience.",
                "answer": "Storytelling",
                "id": 253
            },
            
            {
                "question": "involves fully engaging in an experience or environment to gain a deep understanding of it.",
                "answer": "Immersion",
                "id": 254
            },
            
            {
                "question": "is a creative technique for generating a wide range of ideas and solutions within a group.",
                "answer": "Brainstorming",
                "id": 255
            },
            
            {
                "question": " involve visually representing ideas, concepts, or designs through hand-drawn images.",
                "answer": "Sketching and Drawing",
                "id": 256
            },
            
            {
                "question": "is the way in which a problem or situation is presented, and involves looking at it from different perspectives.",
                "answer": "Framing and Reframing",
                "id": 257
            },
            
            {
                "question": "is the ability to form logical conclusions, and involves drawing specific conclusions from general information.",
                "answer": "Reasoning and Deduction",
                "id": 258
            },
            
            {
                "question": "is the creation of preliminary models or representations of a design or idea, and involves imagining future scenarios.",
                "answer": "Prototyping and Envisioning",
                "id": 259
            },
            
            {
                "question": "involves analyzing and evaluating information or arguments.",
                "answer": "Critical Thinking",
                "id": 260
            },

            {
                "question": "A well-defined process provides a clear path for designing and evaluating user interfaces, ensuring that all relevant aspects are considered.",
                "answer": "Guiding Structure",
                "id": 261
            },

            {
                "question": "A process helps in systematically identifying user needs, conducting research, prototyping, testing, and iterating, leading to more effective HCI solutions.",
                "answer": "Systematic Approach",
                "id": 262
            },

            {
                "question": " Following a consistent process promotes reliability in design outcomes, making it easier to replicate successful designs and avoid errors.",
                "answer": "Reliability and Consistency",
                "id": 263
            },

            {
                "question": "A process can serve as a framework for both newcomers and experienced professionals, helping them understand and teach HCI principles and methods.",
                "answer": "Scaffolding for Learning",
                "id": 264
            },

            {
                "question": "Having a standardized process fosters a common understanding among team members, facilitating collaboration and communication in HCI projects.",
                "answer": "Shared Conception",
                "id": 265
            },

                {
                    "question": "Specific tasks and actions performed within each main activity if the user experience design process.",
                    "answer": "UX Lifecycle Subactivities",
                    "id": 266
                }
            
        ]
    }
}


